Hi!
Yay!
What's up today?
What?
Today we have a new song, a new trico, the ultimate I.M.V.!
Yay!
Tori Tori Tori.
Hatsune Miku
It's full of love.
They say let's all make a karaage that comes close to that bento.
Here comes the story.
It was difficult. The fried chicken.
It was difficult, wasn't it? Kei-chan got angry.
And he changed.
That's right. We did a lot of things.
It's a music video with a storyline.
Shall we get started?
Let's go!
It's my first time. Of course I've never seen it.
Let's watch it together!
Ready!
Push!
Ooh!
Fun!
Cool.
What? What? Something's coming out.
That was a great speech bubble.
That's cool.
It says "cool," people.
I'm getting good eye contact.
It's got the right eye contact.
It's super charming.Super charming.
It's so strong.
It's so, so, so good.
Pinky to the color of your choice.
It's so good!
Four minutes of this is so good.
Hey, look at me.
I know who you are.
When it's your time
La la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la.
Oh!
This looks good!
This looks delicious!
Disteroim V.
Black!
Tea!
Tea in front!
It's so cute!
What do you think? I'm nervous!
I don't know if I'm not supposed to be nervous.
He's so cute.
He's cute.
Oh! It's done! It's done!
It's done!
It's a bit of a cultural mishmash, but it's...
It's delicious.
How do you like it?
Wow!
It's not easy, is it?
Oh!
Oh! It's going up so high!
It's going up so high!
It's going up so high! It's going up so high!
Spread the goodness to the world!Spread the goodness around the world!
Now it's going further, and further, and further!
Doudashi (Japanese soup stock)
Uo-oh-dashi
There really are some things you just can't stop thinking about
Ooh-oh-oh.
What?
Are you crazy?
He's depressed.
That's great, Kensei.
That's great. That's really great.
You scared the shit out of me.
Oh, my God!
That's scary.
Scary.
Aah!
7 people joined the giveaway!
Wow!
Don't be sad.
Ohhhh!
They're here already.
Ahhh...
I'm ready.
This one, this one.
This guy.
They look so happy.
They all look so good.
Oh, my God, they look so good.
You've got it.
Thank you for the food.
Thank you very much for your hard work.
Congratulations.
He's so cute.
It's so cute.It's so cute.
It's love, isn't it?
The scene where he appears is amazing!
I'm so excited.
It's so cool!
Rikiya the mecha finally came out!
He's in the collaboration music video!
He took the liberty of popping in
He went on a field trip.
He said, "Here you go!
The appearance of a trading ball
Kechering Leon
I'm too happy.
The only thing that could fix O-chan's mood was the deal ball.
The only thing that could fix his mood was a trading sphere.
That's a really good movie.
So much fun
Us in the dressing room
Her facial expressions are so good!
They really bring out the true smiles on our faces.
It's amazing.
I think everyone got it, didn't they?
How much we love deal balls.
We've been saying that for years and years.
We love trade ball lunches.
You've been saying that for about two years.
I've been saying it more.
You've been saying it in private for years.
We just started bringing them out.
Just recently.
I didn't mean to hide it from you.
But I finally couldn't take it anymore.
So I started saying it.
I expressed it.
I've liked you from everyone.
But it's hard to find someone you likeIt's not easy to say who you like.
You don't often say who you like in public.
And with someone you like, music videos
People get jealous.
So I tried not to say anything about it.
I even made a music video.
No one can complain.
That's the truth.
You made it last time.
It's thanks to you.
There was a time when I said that to Nee-chan.
The very first one.
Can I just see the first scene?
This one's a little...
I love this one.
How many were born?
There's so many.
What's going on? You're looking at me like I'm crazy.
I thought you were crazy.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'll give you one Chien-Ken.
Chien Keng
Ha-ha-ha
Doyusha
Too cute
You have a nice face.
I can taste it.
Mmm.
I wonder what kind of mate he eats.
It's got the word "mellow" in it.
Yeah.
Mellomellomellomellomellomellomellomellomellomellomellom.
This is serious food. It's not good.
No, it's not.No, it wasn't.
It wasn't that long of a shoot.
I think we all finished our meals.
You say they were forced to eat.
You know, it's like I'm buying the food.
I had to be patient.
It's no use if there's no food left.
That's right.
That's why I knew it.
Then I said, "Give me that," and I'll take one of the other kids'.
I ate at such a high pace
I ate at such a fast pace!
Yes, it's a nice picture.
It's a great song.
It's amazing.
It's like after watching a drama
Like after watching a drama.
What's this?
I want to watch it again and again.
I'm satisfied.
Thank you.
I'm glad.
I hope everyone will watch it a lot.
Maybe you won't notice the expressions on the members' faces at all if you watch it once.
Also, the close-ups of the vegetables and who is cutting what.
I'll stop for a moment.
Surely.
By all means, all the members are cutting.
I'm giving you the flow, too.
I'm giving it to you.
I acted like a real mossy.
Cocking!
Ah!
I've done it many times.
The antics are amazing.
But he still hides his face.But it still hides my face.
To get into the frying pan.
You were actually throwing it.
I made it good every time.
He was throwing everything into the frying pan.
It was good.
It was amazing.
Look at the various parts,
If you have any favorite points, please let us know,
If you have any favorite parts, please let me know,
If you have any comments on the music video, please feel free to leave a comment.
If you think it is a good music video, please click the "Good" button.
Subscribe to our channel!
That's all for now, SHOES!
Bye bye.
Let's go put this one in, too!
me
hmm
mmm?
Mm-mm.
Mm-mm-mm
mmm